Tsuki here,
the proportion
genius
of
Workdol
(The ultimate proportion genius is on standby)
Today, I felt a bit insecure
(For the views)
I had no choice,
it was for the views
(The saviors of views are here)
Guys, come on out
(Ahyeon & Asa / BABYMONSTER)
Have you worked a part-time job before?
I made udon
like this at my mom's sister's shop
(Udon)
Oh really?
(Experienced hire)
Welcome
(No experience)
She turned out to be experienced
Why did you decide to appear on Workdol?
Actually, I’ve been watching
Workdol all the time,
especially when I eat
(Production crew’s self-esteem boost)
- I’ve said this was my pick to appear in
- Really?
They love it so much
(So happy)
Isn’t today’s shoot just awesome?
You mean the vibe’s good?
I’ll just move on
So,
what’s today’s part-time job?
What's today's part-time job?
Spray
It's at a perfume store
- Wow
- Yes
(Don't spray the perfume!)
(Perfume store part-timer)
(Heading to work fast)
Let's go
Hello
We don't have much time,
(Lee Myung-geun (2nd year))
so change into our uniform
and let's get straight to work
(Quick change because we're busy)
What the heck?
(Front row seat to the drama)
What is this?
But I don't even know
what you guys are selling,
or what kind of...
(Holibanum Jamsil perfume store)
We're a domestic perfume brand
(A niche fragrance brand
born from the hands of a perfumer)
If you try selling and get some training,
you'll understand
all the charms of our products
Since you're working at a perfume brand,
do you have any special skills?
I'm kind of
(Famous nose)
famous for my sense of smell
Super nose
So then
Huu
(Damn it...)
Guess what I ate?
You didn't brush your teeth yesterday?
(Super nose's sense of smell is legit)
How did he know?
(Moving inventory)
- This way, please
- Looks kinda heavy
(Starting to load and unload perfume)
- Hello, Mr. driver
- Hi there
Just stack them up neatly
Got it
It's actually heavy
Oh, the box angle's off
(First cart done)
If I drop it,
the perfume will break, right?
Then I guess
you won't get paid for today
Oh my god
(Drop it and bye-bye salary)
How much is all this together?
(Starting the second cart)
Nice, Ahyeon, you got this
Whoa, let’s go!
(Sliding sound)
Oh no, it’s falling!
No, no, no, no!
This thing’s precious
(Nervous)
If even one breaks,
there goes today’s pay
Careful, careful
What if my arm snaps?
- Ugh
- I'm sweating
(Totally worn out)
That's it for today's strength training
(Seriously... workout complete...)
(no exaggeration, suffering for real while moving)
We're heading to our warehouse
(Product inspection)
One person will check,
count the products, then record it
Let's start
Alright
Got it
I seriously didn’t understand a thing
(Workdol MC's level)
- You didn’t get any of it?
- Yes, I was listening, but...
(Explanation again)
Check if the anti-tamper sticker
is attached properly
Put it back in neatly
Count them and let me know
(Old-school)
Why aren’t you bringing them over faster?
Oh, no
(Inspecting)
(Approved)
Yes
Good
Check complete
We’re running out of time
We really have to hold our breath right now
Could you let us breathe a little, please?
(Total boomer)
It's getting harder to breathe
No rest allowed
We don't have time
(You should work too now)
Tsuki, looks like you have to do it too
(Everyone's hustling at work)
(36, all clear)
- All done?
- Yes
That was fast
Of course
Then,
(Haze)
why don't you show us a trick?
Show us
(Doesn't back down)
Please
just once
I want...
(Outrageous trick)
(Second round)
Please don't kick me out
(Break time)
(After work, it's girls' tea time)
Honestly,
to be real,
your concerts are way bigger than ours
Okay?
(Oh... Ah...)
But you know you can't
ignore us at music shows, right?
Still, seniority is seniority,
you know?
Yep
No, you got to greet us properly
and when we run into
each other at music shows,
(Teaching BABYMONSTER discipline)
I'll bow at a 90-degree angle
But I heard there is some good news
(Homework time)
(Quick promo time)
Let me just do a quick one
Honestly, this is the main thing, right?
No
We're here just to do a part-time job today
(Then promo confiscated)
Then maybe you don't need to do it
We were building up to this, though?
(BABYMONSTER - HOT SAUCE promo)
It's got a bubbly 90s hip-hop vibe
that's perfect for summer
(Interesting)
(Self-promo)
That's it for now
(Whatever, tell us a fun story)
Any fun stories?
(Ahyeon's fun story)
So I got caught eating ramen at work
They told me to write a reflection letter
about how I ended up eating it
So...
(Already awkward)
So
I wanted some ramen
so I went to the convenience store,
but now I had to
write about it in detail
(Ahyeon's reflection)
I bought ramen
I sprinkled in the powder
I ate some ramen, and it was tasty.
That's it, right?
(Unexpected recipe drop)
I wrote it like that and got scolded
(Remembering a funny convo)
Same here, seriously
(Uneasy)
Yes
Asa
Do you have two butts or one?
Haha, that's so random
(Butt victim)
But seriously,
Asa unnie thought
it was really important,
so she went around asking every member
about it for a while
Oh really?
- I think there are two
- Why two?
There's just one
(There is one/ There are two)
No,
- you got to combine these
- It's one
(There are two)
But since
there are two legs,
there's kind of a split, you know?
She says there's a split
(Stop overthinking)
But it could just be a wrinkle
(Store prep)
Could you try doing a display?
Please decorate it artistically
(Starting to decorate the product)
All right
(Lime scent tester)
Lime
Here it is
First, do this in a zigzag motion
(Unleashing artistic spirit)
- In a zigzag motion
- Nice
(Store getting pretty crowded)
- There are too many, way too many
- We have a lot of scents
There’s also a new scent launching soon
What’s the new one that’s coming out?
The new one coming out
is called Noir Banana
(Noir Banana:
Creamy vanilla-scented tobacco,
dreamy smoky woody scent)
Banana, banana-na ♫
(What the...?)
Banana banana-na ♫
Banana ♫
(Reality check)
Potato
(Workdol is tough)
We got to start selling for real now
(Perfume sales training)
Usually, you look at the customer's vibe
and recommend a scent
that you think would suit them
So, I'll give it a try
Okay
This is a roleplay
(Idol-looking customer enters)
Hi, since it's summer,
I'd love to smell something nice
and fragrant instead of sweat
(Face-reading check)
In that case,
something that matches your image
(Ginger Holiday:
The fresh, subtle scent of lilac,
clean soap fragrance)
It's blended from 11 different scents
So if you try it,
you'll notice ginger
(Paradise)
as the base
but it's a really luxurious scent
Wow, it's like deodorant
How am I supposed to describe this scent?
Just describe it
however you feel
So, can I just say
it's an expensive perfume?
(Thinking)
Smells like a fancy perfume
Yes, that's right
Do you want to seem fancy?
(Recommendation)
Since you look kinda cheap!
That one’s a no-go
You just got to compliment no matter what
(Next customer is a Japanese customer)
Japanese customer
What would be good?
Can you speak Korean?
(Can't understand)
(Fancy +1)
Gyaru
(Cool +1)
(Charisma +1)
(Kawaii +1)
Sweet, maybe?
(Escaping from training)
I think that's enough for training
When you sell after putting on the perfume,
(Strategy: seduce customers with fragrance)
customers will get curious about our scent
My top pick is the signature scent,
Summer Break
(Summer Break:
A sweet and tangy half-cut peach scent)
It honestly just smells like
you’re holding a real peach
(Asa PICK Summer Break)
So, we’re spraying this one, right?
(Dousing themselves in perfume)
It's too much
That’s way too much
I want to go
for a more luxurious vibe
That's Ginger
(Tsuki PICK Ginger Holiday)
(Loaded with rich vibes)
You know what I mean, right?
Which one?
Rose? Should we?
Oh, Rose?
Alright
(Ahyeon picks Rosy Blossom)
Where should I spray this?
Oh, seriously
Geez
Not on the face
It's not a mist
That scared me
I thought it was
a cosmetics commercial, for real
(Moisture fully recharged)
- Did you see?
- Yes, on your face
(Welcoming guests)
Welcome
(Flustered)
Hello
Ta-da
Welcome
Welcome to Holibanum
That was so touching
You enjoyed it, right?
Okay, so now
you just need to buy a perfume
(Truly cold-hearted capitalism)
I have to buy one?
(Perfume newbie)
But I don't really use perfume that much
(Prefers mist)
As someone
who doesn't use perfume often,
I'd recommend Summer Break
(Highly recommended)
as the easiest one to start with
What kind of scent is it?
We got to spray it for her
Tssk
(Ahyeon going all out with energy today)
(Super satisfied)
All done
My hands feel so soft
Ah
Peach?
Oh, yes, that's right
Yes, that's true
Do you have a boyfriend?
No
If you spray it,
everyone will...
- What?!
- Exactly
(Turns around to check the scent)
Who's that person?
I could totally see the future
(Congrats in advance)
- Congrats
- Does that mean I can get a boyfriend right away?
(Chance of getting back together)
There’s even a perfume
that can make your ex-boyfriend
come back to you
Was there an ex
you wanted to get back together with?
Huh?
Guess there is!
(Video letter cliché)
Send a message to him
How are you doing?
Oh my
- Yes, I'm doing well
- Oh my
We were supposed to get a meal together
Maybe later
(Looks like they still can't forget each other...)
You haven't eaten yet?
- They haven't eaten yet
- They haven't eaten yet, really?
What are you doing?
Come get her right now
Then are you gonna buy it?
(Capitalism)
Excuse me
Are you gonna buy it?
(Break-up line)
Can I think about it a little more?
Oh, of course, that’s totally fine
(Another goodbye...)
We’ll be waiting
No...
- Don’t go
You did so well
Very well
(Breakup prevention pro tip)
Let me give you a tip
At this store only,
you get a 10% discount,
and if you buy a perfume,
you get a free 9ml mini perfume
Why didn’t you say that earlier?
(Nervous)
I was gonna mention it
after seeing you sell something
(Meanwhile, a customer walks in)
Okay
1, 2, 3, 4
Welcome
Welcome to Holibanum
Do you have any recommendations?
(Pink)
It seems like you like
pink stuff,
so I'd like to recommend this perfume
Rosy Blossom
It's Brrrrlossom
Blossom
(An introvert's survival story
in a variety show)
How is it?
It's good
- Something a bit lighter?
- Something light
Can I make a suggestion?
(Excited)
I nailed the point
This bag
Oh my
What comes to mind?
Banana
(Presenting Noir Banana)
I thought of a banana. Here, take this
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
(CM song playing)
Banana, banana-na ♫
(Their performance reaching its peak)
Potato
Banana, banana-na ♫
How is it?
Do you like the scent?
Yes, it has a subtle banana fragrance
(Total customer satisfaction)
It's so natural
(Manager barges in)
Please tell her about the benefits
I already shared the secret move
If you buy this,
actually,
the
manager here
will buy it for you
He'll buy it for me?
(An insane 90% off)
Just pay 10%
(What a steal)
thanks to a 90% discount
If you want, you can get this manager
(Manager included as a freebie)
as a buy one, get one free deal
I have a boyfriend
Oh really?
Not even as a spare?
(...You think?)
That's tough
So, will you make a purchase?
Oh
Yes
(First successful sale)
Thank you
(Serving more customers)
Do you have any sweet scents?
Yes, we do
- It's no joke, seriously
- Here, smell this
(Sniffing)
Whoa,
flowers just bloomed behind you
Roses
(Quick purchase after the compliments)
(Next up is Office Girl)
If you work at an office,
there's a perfume that really suits you
Ginger Holiday
Wow, look at all that treasure in the back
- Wow
- What do you think?
I love it
(Another quick purchase here)
Thank you, have a great day
We're actually
high school students
(Nice to meet you, friend)
(Exam takers)
Is there something
that can clear your mind,
make you feel refreshed?
(Noir Banana recommendation)
This one
Oh, awesome
Seriously, I want to buy it
It's 79,000 won
Sorry
(Quick release)
Thank you
Ahyeon is dead
(Resurrected)
Crazy energy
Nope
No,
I’m totally fine right now
(Today’s last guest)
Hello
(Reading the room)
Welcome
- Hello
- How do you two
know each other?
(Awkward pause)
We’re
a couple
(Over-the-top reaction)
My heart just started pounding
Ba-dum
(Just using the reaction
as an excuse to fool around)
(Q. What kind of perfume do you want?)
- What perfume?
- Love?
Something that can make our love
become a bit stronger?
(We'll let you know!)
- Just a moment to think
- I’ll think about it
Do you argue normally,
occasionally?
A little
A little?
I think they need a sweet scent
A touch of sweetness
This one?
Summer
Break
(Adding some sweetness)
(All done)
Go ahead
(Love is being restored)
- Is it good?
- Yes
I think this one’s the best
Really?
Would you consider buying it?
Well, I wouldn’t just buy it,
but Ahyeon, you sing so well
(Extorting a song from Ahyeon)
Ahyeon’s song?
Something that could make
love grow even more
(Glancing around)
If it’s a dangerous love,
you got to sing Dangerously
(Charlie Puth - Dangerously
No holding back)
We hope you last long
(Stay tangled up, for real!)
We hope your dangerous love
lasts a long time
(Off work)
It's over
(Time to go home)
We're done
Money, money
Money, please
(That thrill of getting paid)
Thank you
Do whatever you want with this
Ahyeon, anything you want
(Opens envelope)
Hourly wage is 12,000 won,
you worked 6 hours,
so that's 72,000 won,
but they gave you a 10,000 won bonus
(Perfume store pay:
12,000 won hourly x 6 hours
+ 10,000 won bonus = 82,000 won total)
So what are you gonna do with it?
I'm going to put it into savings
Every little bit adds up, you know
(Ambitious girl)
I'm gonna buy something bigger later
What about you, Ahyeon?
Me? First,
I’d
save it up too
(Saving up in my belly)
and maybe use it for food or something
Part-time job recommendation score
Should we talk it over together?
I smelled so many scents
- that I got a little dizzy
- Dizziness
But I also got to smell the scents
that make people happy, right?
So I think it’s a job with a really high
satisfaction level because of that
Then
(Perfume part-time job rating: 4.5/5
Smelling nice scents 5.0, smelling too much 3.5,
getting happy with people 5.0)
For today’s ending pose,
let’s play the Cleopatra game
where you can go all in for first place
(First!)
Hi, Cleopatra
The best potato chips in the world
Oh no
Hi, Cleopatra
The best potato chips in the world
Patra
the world's best...
(Farewell this world...)
(Goodbye, Tsuki)
(Why we live separately)
Does everyone live separately? Or alone?
Now we each have our own rooms,
and the dorm is split into two places
Have you ever fought with the members?
Back when we were trainees,
when we were really young,
You fought?
we fought a lot
Are you all living together in the dorm now?
We all live alone
This is veterans
This is to keep the team together
(Billy’s dorm, full of energy)
It was the company’s decision
to keep the team together
(T saves the world)
Tsuki said that
if a close friend committed a crime
while she was a cop,
she wouldn’t arrest them
(The police episode will be released next week)
What if your girlfriend
is on a date with you
and secretly steals something
right next to you?
I would probably
just hit them with the taser
instead of actually using it
So Tsuki, you wouldn’t arrest them?
(ENFP)
How am I supposed to catch them?
Say it's your boyfriend or girlfriend
Someone you love, like family or whatever
(Sticky fingers ON)
- Oh my
- Ah, theft
But you're a cop
(ENTP)
You're a cop, right?
My boyfriend just stole something,
and I think he should be arrested
(Strictly T)
Really?
I don't think I'd let it slide
(ISTJ)
If there's compensation money...
(Bounty hunter)